<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StudyBuddy AI</string>
    <string name="app_title">StudyBuddy AI</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Ver. 2.1 (Beta)</string>
    <string name="no_account_text">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="terms_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="interpretation">
        The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_1">
        For the purposes of these Terms and Conditions:
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_2">
        <b>Application</b> means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named Aivy.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_3">
        <b>Application Store</b> means the digital distribution service operated and developed by Apple Inc. (Apple App Store) or Google Inc. (Google Play Store) in which the Application has been downloaded.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_4">
        <b>Affiliate</b> means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where "control" means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_5">
        <b>Country</b> refers to: Philippines
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_6">
        <b>Company</b> (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to Aivy.
    </string>

    <string name="definitions_7">
        <b>Device</b> means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_8">
        <b>Service</b> refers to the Application.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_9">
        <b>Terms and Conditions</b> (also referred as "Terms") mean these Terms and Conditions that form the entire agreement between You and the Company regarding the use of the Service. This Terms and Conditions agreement has been created with the help of the TermsFeed Terms and Conditions Generator.
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_10">
        <b>Third-party Social Media Service</b> means any services or content (including data, information, products or services) provided by a third-party that may be displayed, included or made available by the Service
    </string>
    <string name="definitions_11">
        <b>You</b> means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
    </string>

    <string name="definitions_12">
        These are the Terms and Conditions governing the use of this Service and the agreement that operates between You and the Company. These Terms and Conditions set out the rights and obligations of all users regarding the use of the Service. \n \n Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on Your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service. \n \n By accessing or using the Service You agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If You disagree with any part of these Terms and Conditions then You may not access the Service. \n \n You represent that you are over the age of 18. The Company does not permit those under 18 to use the Service. \n \n Your access to and use of the Service is also conditioned on Your acceptance of and compliance with the Privacy Policy of the Company. Our Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your personal information when You use the Application or the Website and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You. Please read Our Privacy Policy carefully before using Our Service. \n \n Links to Other Websites \n \n Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by the Company. \n \n The Company has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that the Company shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services. \n \n We strongly advise You to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that You visit.
    </string>

    <string name="definitions_13">
        Termination \n \n We may terminate or suspend Your access immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if You breach these Terms and Conditions. \n \n Upon termination, Your right to use the Service will cease immediately. \n \n Limitation of Liability \n \n Notwithstanding any damages that You might incur, the entire liability of the Company and any of its suppliers under any provision of this Terms and Your exclusive remedy for all of the foregoing shall be limited to the amount actually paid by You through the Service or 100 USD if You haven\'t purchased anything through the Service. \n \n To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, in no event shall the Company or its suppliers be liable for any special, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages whatsoever (including, but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, loss of data or other information, for business interruption, for personal injury, loss of privacy arising out of or in any way related to the use of or inability to use the Service, third-party software and/or third-party hardware used with the Service, or otherwise in connection with any provision of this Terms), even if the Company or any supplier has been advised of the possibility of such damages and even if the remedy fails of its essential purpose.
    </string>

    <string name="definitions_14">
        Some states do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties or limitation of liability for incidental or consequential damages, which means that some of the above limitations may not apply. In these states, each party\'s liability will be limited to the greatest extent permitted by law. \n \n "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" Disclaimer \n \n The Service is provided to You "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" and with all faults and defects without warranty of any kind. To the maximum extent permitted under applicable law, the Company, on its own behalf and on behalf of its Affiliates and its and their respective licensors and service providers, expressly disclaims all warranties, whether express, implied, statutory or otherwise, with respect to the Service, including all implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement, and warranties that may arise out of course of dealing, course of performance, usage or trade practice. Without limitation to the foregoing, the Company provides no warranty or undertaking, and makes no representation of any kind that the Service will meet Your requirements, achieve any intended results, be compatible or work with any other software, applications, systems or services, operate without interruption, meet any performance or reliability standards or be error free or that any errors or defects can or will be corrected. \n \n Without limiting the foregoing, neither the Company nor any of the company\'s provider makes any representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied: (i) as to the operation or availability of the Service, or the information, content, and materials or products included thereon; (ii) that the Service will be uninterrupted or error-free; (iii) as to the accuracy, reliability, or currency of any information or content provided through the Service; or (iv) that the Service, its servers, the content, or e-mails sent from or on behalf of the Company are free of viruses, scripts, trojan horses, worms, malware, timebombs or other harmful components. \n \n Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain types of warranties or limitations on applicable statutory rights of a consumer, so some or all of the above exclusions and limitations may not apply to You. But in such a case the exclusions and limitations set forth in this section shall be applied to the greatest extent enforceable under applicable law. \n \n Governing Law \n \n The laws of the Country, excluding its conflicts of law rules, shall govern this Terms and Your use of the Service. Your use of the Application may also be subject to other local, state, national, or international laws. \n \n Disputes Resolution \n \n If You have any concern or dispute about the Service, You agree to first try to resolve the dispute informally by contacting the Company. \n \n For European Union (EU) Users \n \n If You are a European Union consumer, you will benefit from any mandatory provisions of the law of the country in which you are resident in. \n \n United States Legal Compliance \n \n You represent and warrant that (i) You are not located in a country that is subject to the United States government embargo, or that has been designated by the United States government as a "terrorist supporting" country, and (ii) You are not listed on any United States government list of prohibited or restricted parties. \n \n Severability and Waiver
    </string>

    <string name="severability">
        If any provision of these Terms is held to be unenforceable or invalid, such provision will be changed and interpreted to accomplish the objectives of such provision to the greatest extent possible under applicable law and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.
    </string>
    
    <string name="waiver">
        Except as provided herein, the failure to exercise a right or to require performance of an obligation under these Terms shall not effect a party\'s ability to exercise such right or require such performance at any time thereafter nor shall the waiver of a breach constitute a waiver of any subsequent breach. \n \n Translation Interpretation \n \n These Terms and Conditions may have been translated if We have made them available to You on our Service. You agree that the original English text shall prevail in the case of a dispute. \n \n Changes to These Terms and Conditions \n \n We reserve the right, at Our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material We will make reasonable efforts to provide at least 30 days\' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at Our sole discretion. \n \n By continuing to access or use Our Service after those revisions become effective, You agree to be bound by the revised terms. If You do not agree to the new terms, in whole or in part, please stop using the website and the Service. \n \n Contact Us \n \n If you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, You can contact us: \n \n - By email: studybuddy.aivy@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string name="separator">
        ---------------------------------------------------------
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_1">
        This privacy notice for StudyBuddy Al ("Company," "we," "us," or "our"), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share ("process") your information when you use our services ("Services"), such as when you: \n \n • Download and use our Facebook application (StudyBuddy Al), or any other application of ours that links to this privacy notice \n \n • Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events \n \n Questions or concerns? Reading this privacy notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [studybuddy.aivy@gmail.com](mailto:studybuddy.aivy@gmail.com). \n \n SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS \n \n This summary provides key points from our privacy notice, but you can find out more details about any of these topics by clicking the link following each key point or by using our table of contents below to find the section you are looking for. \n \n <b>What personal information do we process?</b> When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process personal information depending on how you interact with StudyBuddy Al and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. Click here to learn more. \n \n <b>Do we process any sensitive personal information?</b> We may process sensitive personal information when necessary with your consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. \n \n <b>Do we receive any information from third parties?</b> We do not receive any information from third parties. \n \n <b>How do we process your information?</b> We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent. We process your information only when we have a valid legal reason to do so. \n \n <b>In what situations and with which parties do we share personal information?</b> We may share information in specific situations and with specific third parties. \n \n <b>What are your rights?</b> Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean you have certain rights regarding your personal information. \n \n <b>How do you exercise your rights?</b> The easiest way to exercise your rights is by filling out our data subject request form available here, or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_2">
        \n TABLE OF CONTENTS \n \n 1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT? \n \n 2. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION? \n \n 3. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? \n \n 4. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS? \n \n 5. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION? \n \n 6. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS? \n \n 7. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS? \n \n 8. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES \n \n 9. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS? \n \n 10. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE? \n \n 11. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE? \n \n 12. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_3">
        Personal information you disclose to us \n\n In Short: We collect personal information that you provide to us. \n\n We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you express an interest in obtaining information \n\n about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us. \n\n Personal Information Provided by You. The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following: \n\n - names \n\n Sensitive Information. When necessary, with your consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law, we process the following categories of sensitive information: \n\n -health data \n\n -student data \n\n -data about a person\'s sex life or sexual orientation \n\n -biometric data \n\n -information revealing political opinions \n\n Social Media Login Data. We may provide you with the option to register with us using your existing social media account details, like your Facebook, Twitter, or other social media account. If you choose to register in this way, we will collect the information described in the section called "HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?" below. \n\n Application Data. If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission: \n\n - Push Notifications. We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or certain features of the application(s). If you wish to opt out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device\'s settings. \n\n This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes. \n\n All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information. \n\n Information collected when you use our Facebook application(s). We by default access your Facebook basic account information, including your name, email, gender, birthday, current city, and profile picture URL, as well as other information that you choose to make public. We may also request access to other permissions related to your account, such as friends, check-ins, and likes, and you may choose to grant or deny us access to each individual permission. For more information regarding Facebook permissions, refer to the Facebook Permissions Reference page.
    </string>

</resources>